<Presentation PresentationClass="profile">
  <PageOptions Columns="2"/>
  <WindowName>About</WindowName>  
  <PageTitle>Need Help?</PageTitle>
  <PageBackLinkName></PageBackLinkName>
  <PageBackLinkURL></PageBackLinkURL>
  <PageSubTitle></PageSubTitle>
  <PageDescription></PageDescription>  
  <PanelList>
    <Panel type="header"  />
    <Panel type="page" />
    <Panel Type="active">
      <Module ID="MainMenu"/>
    </Panel>
    <Panel Type="main">
      <Module ID="HTMLBlock">
        <ParamList>
          <Param Name="HTML">

<script type="text/javascript">
$('#suckerfishmenu li#contact a').addClass('active'); 
$('.profiles .profilesContentMain .pageTitle h2').hide();
</script>

  <div class="content-block-container">
	  <div class="content-block">
		<h2 style="font-size:30px">Need Help?</h2>
		<p><strong>Publications</strong>: To add, remove, or fix a publication, 
		   <strong><a href="../login/default.aspx?method=login&amp;edit=true">sign in to edit</a></strong> your profile page.
		</p>
		<p><strong>Photo</strong>: To add or remove a photo, 
		   <strong><a href="../login/default.aspx?method=login&amp;edit=true">sign in to edit</a></strong> your profile page.
		</p>
		<p><strong>Name/Degree/Contact Information</strong>: We get this data from the UCLA HR system(s). Ask your HR 
		   representative to make those changes or ask your UCLA campus department how to make changes to your HR record. 
		</p>
		<p><a href="#faq" class="dblarrow">Frequently Asked Questions</a></p>
	  </div>
	 
	  <div class="content-block">
		<h2 style="font-size:30px">Contact Us</h2>
		<p>Please <a href="mailto:profiles@ucla.edu">share your feedback</a> about how to improve
		   UCLA Profiles, and let us know if UCLA Profiles has enabled your research in any way.
		   Your success stories are important to enable the continued support and expansion of this
		   important tool.
		</p>
		<p><strong>Email us at <a href="mailto:profiles@ucla.edu">profiles@ucla.edu</a></strong></p>
	  </div>
	</div>

<h2 style="clear:left; padding-top:20px;">Researcher Information</h2>
<p>An individual's profile page shows data drawn from external sources, and may also display 
custom content added by the researcher.</p> 

<table width="940">
<tr>
<td valign="top" style="font-size:12px;line-height:16px;padding-top:23px;">
Name, degrees and contact information are imported from campus systems. <br /><br />
Profile owners may add:
<ul class="square" style="font-size:12px;line-height:16px;margin:0;">
<li>Photo</li>
<li>Education and Training</li>
<li>Awards and Honors</li>
<li>Research Overview</li>
<li>Interests</li>
<li>Featured Publications</li>
<li>Faculty Mentoring</li>
<li>Student Projects</li>
<li>Twitter and other feeds</li>
<li>Videos</li>
<li>Websites</li>
<li>News Links</li>
</ul>
<br />
Research Activities and Funding come from NIH ExPORTER. Other grants <br />may be added.
<br /><br /><br />Published articles available <br />
in PubMed are listed automatically. Other <span style="white-space:nowrap">publications may be added.</span>
</td>
<td valign="top"><img src="images/profilesnapshot.png" width="600" alt="" /></td>
<td valign="top" style="font-size:12px;line-height:16px;padding-top:23px;">
Networks are generated from research available in PubMed.
<br /><br /><br />
Research concepts/topics <span style="white-space:nowrap">based on PubMed MeSH terms</span><br /><br /><br /><br />
Co-authors from the same institution<br /><br /><br /><br /><br /><br />
Co-authors from external institutions<br /><br /><br /><br /><br /><br />
Researchers working on the same topics
</td>
</tr>
</table>
<p>Many researchers also have Clinical Trials information based on trials listed in clinicaltrials.gov.</p>

<h2 class="about" id="faq">Frequently Asked Questions</h2>
<ul> 
  <li><a href="#who">Who is listed in UCLA Profiles?</a></li>
  <li><a href="#view">Who can view UCLA Profiles?</a></li>
  <li><a href="#login">How do I sign in to UCLA Profiles?</a></li>
  <li><a href="#pubs">Why are there missing or incorrect publications in my profile? How can I correct this?</a></li>
  <li><a href="#proxy">Can someone manage my profile page for me?</a></li>
  <li><a href="#manage">Who manages UCLA Profiles?</a></li>
</ul>

<h3 id="who">Who is listed in UCLA Profiles?</h3>

<ul>
  <li>UCLA Profiles was created for research networking so we initially focused on adding UCLA faculty members, 
  researchers with academic leadership appointments, and non-faculty academic researchers. </li>
  <li>We are happy to include research staff and other individuals in the UCLA community, on request and if possible. 
  Send requests, with full name and employee ID, to <a href="mailto:profiles@ucla.edu">profiles@ucla.edu</a></li>
</ul>

<h3 id="view">Who can view UCLA Profiles?</h3>
<ul>
  <li>UCLA Profiles is searchable on the web and can be viewed by the general public as well as the UCLA community.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="login">How do I sign in to UCLA Profiles?</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Click the <strong><a href="../login/default.aspx?method=login&amp;edit=true">Sign in</a></strong> link on any UCLA Profiles page.
  Then enter your single sign on (SSO) username and password.</li>
  <li>If you have never used SSO, or for password support, go to 
  <a href="https://www.it.ucla.edu/services/accounts-access/ucla-logon-id" target="_blank">UCLA Logon ID</a> 
  or contact your Home Departmental Administrator.</li> 
</ul>

<h3 id="pubs">Why are there missing or incorrect publications in my profile? How can I correct this?</h3> 
<ul>
  <li>UCLA Profiles uses a complex mix of names, institution, and publication information to find your  publications in PubMed's repository. 
  Unfortunately, there is no easy way to  match all articles in PubMed to Profiles authors with complete precision and accuracy. </li>
  <li>People who have common names, who published under multiple names or whose articles were written while at other 
  institutions are most likely to have incomplete publication lists. </li>
  <li>You can make corrections by searching PubMed from within Profiles to add, edit or delete publications. By curating publications 
  manually, you are helping UCLA Profiles to identify which concepts and co-authors are correctly associated with your profile, 
  thereby increasing the likelihood of finding the right publications on subsequent attempts. </li>
  <li><strong>NOTE</strong>: If you would like to add publications, grants, clinical trials or other examples of your scholarly activity that are not in 
  MEDLINE/PubMed, NIH Reporter, or clinicaltrials.gov, you can add them manually in the appropriate section, or in your Overview.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="proxy">Can someone manage my profile page for me?</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Yes. Proxies are people within Profiles who can edit other people's profiles on their behalf. For example, faculty can designate 
  their assistants as proxies to edit their profiles. If you have a profile, then one or more proxies might be assigned to you automatically 
  by your department or institution. You also have the option of designating your own proxies by signing in and going to Manage Proxies in 
  the edit menu. Proxies do not need to have profile pages themselves.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="manage">Who manages UCLA Profiles?</h3>
<ul>
  <li>UCLA Profiles is managed by the <a href="https://ctsi.ucsf.edu/about-us/programs/research-technology" target="_blank">Research Technology</a> 
  program of UCSF's <a href="http://ctsi.ucsf.edu" target="_blank">Clinical and Translational Science Institute (CTSI)</a>.</li>
</ul>

          </Param>
        </ParamList>
      </Module>
      <Panel Type="passive"/>
      <Panel type="footer" />
    </Panel> 
  </PanelList>
</Presentation>

