<Presentation PresentationClass="profile">
  <PageOptions Columns="2"/>
  <WindowName>About</WindowName>  
  <PageTitle>Need Help?</PageTitle>
  <PageBackLinkName></PageBackLinkName>
  <PageBackLinkURL></PageBackLinkURL>
  <PageSubTitle></PageSubTitle>
  <PageDescription></PageDescription>  
  <PanelList>
    <Panel type="header"  />
    <Panel type="page" />
    <Panel Type="active">
      <Module ID="MainMenu"/>
    </Panel>
    <Panel Type="main">
      <Module ID="HTMLBlock">
        <ParamList>
          <Param Name="HTML">

<script type="text/javascript">
$('#suckerfishmenu li#contact a').addClass('active'); 
$('.profiles .profilesContentMain .pageTitle h2').hide();
</script>

	<div class="content-block-container">
	  <div class="content-block">
		<h2 style="font-size:30px">Need Help?</h2>
		<p><strong>Publications</strong>: To add, remove, or fix a publication, 
		   <strong><a href="../login/default.aspx?method=login&amp;edit=true">sign in to edit</a></strong> your profile page.
		</p>
		<p><strong>Photo</strong>: To add or remove a photo, 
		   <strong><a href="../login/default.aspx?method=login&amp;edit=true">sign in to edit</a></strong> your profile page.
		</p>
		<p><strong>Name/Degree/Contact Information</strong>: We get this data from the UC Davis HR system(s). Ask your HR 
		   representative to make those changes or ask your UC Davis campus department how to make changes to your HR record. 
		</p>
		<p><a href="#faq" class="dblarrow">Frequently Asked Questions</a></p>
	  </div>
	 
	  <div class="content-block">
		<h2 style="font-size:30px">Contact Us</h2>
		<p>Please <a href="mailto:profiles@ucdavis.edu">share your feedback</a> about how to improve
		   UC Davis Profiles, and let us know if UC Davis Profiles has enabled your research in any way.
		   Your success stories are important to enable the continued support and expansion of this
		   important tool.
		</p>
		<p><strong>Email us at <a href="mailto:profiles@ucdavis.edu">profiles@ucdavis.edu</a></strong></p>
	  </div>
	</div>

<h2 style="clear:left; padding-top:20px;">Researcher Information</h2>
<p>An individual's profile page shows data drawn from external sources, and may also display 
custom content added by the researcher.</p> 

<table width="940">
<tr>
<td valign="top" style="font-size:12px;line-height:16px;padding-top:23px;">
Name, degrees and contact information are imported from campus systems. <br /><br />
Profile owners may add:
<ul class="square" style="font-size:12px;line-height:16px;margin:0;">
<li>Photo</li>
<li>Education and Training</li>
<li>Awards and Honors</li>
<li>Research Overview</li>
<li>Interests</li>
<li>Featured Publications</li>
<li>Faculty Mentoring</li>
<li>Student Projects</li>
<li>Twitter and other feeds</li>
<li>Videos</li>
<li>Websites</li>
<li>News Links</li>
</ul>
<br />
Research Activities and Funding come from NIH ExPORTER. Other grants <br />may be added.
<br /><br /><br />Published articles available <br />
in PubMed are listed automatically. Other <span style="white-space:nowrap">publications may be added.</span>
</td>
<td valign="top"><img src="images/profilesnapshot.png" width="600" alt="" /></td>
<td valign="top" style="font-size:12px;line-height:16px;padding-top:23px;">
Networks are generated from research available in PubMed.
<br /><br /><br />
Research concepts/topics <span style="white-space:nowrap">based on PubMed MeSH terms</span><br /><br /><br /><br />
Co-authors from the same institution<br /><br /><br /><br /><br /><br />
Co-authors from external institutions<br /><br /><br /><br /><br /><br />
Researchers working on the same topics
</td>
</tr>
</table>
<p>Many researchers also have Clinical Trials information based on trials listed in clinicaltrials.gov.</p>

<h2 class="about" id="faq">Frequently Asked Questions</h2>
<ul> 
  <li><a href="#who">Who is listed in UC Davis Profiles?</a></li>
  <li><a href="#view">Who can view UC Davis Profiles?</a></li>
  <li><a href="#login">How do I sign in to UC Davis Profiles?</a></li>
  <li><a href="#pubs">Why are there missing or incorrect publications in my profile? How can I correct this?</a></li>
  <li><a href="#manage">Who manages UC Davis Profiles?</a></li>
</ul>

<h3 id="who">Who is listed in UC Davis Profiles?</h3>

<ul>
  <li>UC Davis Profiles was created for research networking so we initially focused on adding UC Davis faculty members, 
  researchers with academic leadership appointments, and non-faculty academic researchers. </li>
  <li>We are happy to include research staff and other individuals in the UC Davis community, on request and if possible. 
  Send requests, with full name and employee ID, to <a href="mailto:profiles@ucdavis.edu">profiles@ucdavis.edu</a></li>
</ul>

<h3 id="view">Who can view UC Davis Profiles?</h3>
<ul>
  <li>UC Davis Profiles is searchable on the web and can be viewed by the general public as well as the UC Davis community.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="login">How do I sign in to UC Davis Profiles?</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Click the <strong><a href="../login/default.aspx?method=login&amp;edit=true">Sign in</a></strong> link on any UC Davis Profiles page.
  Then enter your single sign on (SSO) username and password.</li>
  <li>If you have never used SSO, or for password support, go to 
  <a href="http://iaminfo.ucdavis.edu/faq.cfm" target="_blank">UC Davis Identity and Access Management</a> 
  or contact your Home Departmental Administrator.</li> 
</ul>

<h3 id="pubs">Why are there missing or incorrect publications in my profile? How can I correct this?</h3> 
<ul>
  <li>UC Davis Profiles uses a complex mix of names, institution, and publication information to find your  publications in PubMed's repository. 
  Unfortunately, there is no easy way to  match all articles in PubMed to Profiles authors with complete precision and accuracy. </li>
  <li>People who have common names, who published under multiple names or whose articles were written while at other 
  institutions are most likely to have incomplete publication lists. </li>
  <li>You can make corrections by searching PubMed from within Profiles to add, edit or delete publications. By curating publications 
  manually, you are helping UC Davis Profiles to identify which concepts and co-authors are correctly associated with your profile, 
  thereby increasing the likelihood of finding the right publications on subsequent attempts. </li>
</ul>

<h3 id="manage">Who manages UC Davis Profiles?</h3>
<ul>
  <li>UC Davis Profiles is managed by the Research Technology program of UCSF's Clinical and Translational Science Institute (CTSI) 
  on behalf of the UC Davis <a href="http://www.ucdmc.ucdavis.edu/ctsc/index.html" target="_blank">Clinical and Translational Science Center</a>. </li>
</ul>

          </Param>
        </ParamList>
      </Module>
      <Panel Type="passive"/>
      <Panel type="footer" />
    </Panel> 
  </PanelList>
</Presentation>

