<Presentation PresentationClass="profile">
  <PageOptions Columns="2"/>
  <WindowName>About</WindowName>  
  <PageTitle>Contact Us</PageTitle>
  <PageBackLinkName></PageBackLinkName>
  <PageBackLinkURL></PageBackLinkURL>
  <PageSubTitle></PageSubTitle>
  <PageDescription></PageDescription>  
  <PanelList>
    <Panel type="header"  />
    <Panel type="page" />
    <Panel Type="active">
      <Module ID="MainMenu"/>
    </Panel>
    <Panel Type="main">
      <Module ID="HTMLBlock">
        <ParamList>
          <Param Name="HTML">

<script type="text/javascript">
$('#suckerfishmenu li#contact a').addClass('active'); 
$('.profiles .profilesContentMain .pageTitle h2').hide();
</script>

  <div class="content-block-container">
	  <div class="content-block">
		<h2 style="font-size:30px">Need Help?</h2>
		<p><strong>Publications</strong>: To add, remove, or fix a publication, 
		   <a href="../login/default.aspx?method=login&amp;edit=true">sign in to edit</a> your profile page.
		</p>
		<p><strong>Photo</strong>: To add or remove a photo, 
		   <a href="../login/default.aspx?method=login&amp;edit=true">sign in to edit</a> your profile page.
		</p>
		<p><strong>Name/Degree/Contact Information</strong>: We get this data from the UCSD Directory (Blink). 
			Changes to your data should be directed to the Payroll/Personnel Analyst for 
			your UCSD campus department. If unsure who this person is, contact your department's Business Officer. 
		</p>
		<p><a href="#faq" class="dblarrow">Frequently Asked Questions</a></p>
	  </div>
	 
	  <div class="content-block">
		<h2 style="font-size:30px">Contact Us</h2>
		<p>Please <a href="mailto:ctri-support@ucsd.edu">share your feedback</a> about how to improve
		   UCSD Profiles, and let us know if UCSD Profiles has enabled your research in any way.
		   Your success stories are important to enable the continued support and expansion of this
		   important tool.
		</p>
		<p><strong>Email us at <a href="mailto:ctri-support@ucsd.edu">ctri-support@ucsd.edu</a></strong></p>
	  </div>
	</div>

<h2 style="clear:left; padding-top:20px;">Researcher Information</h2>
<p>An individual's profile page shows data drawn from external sources, and may also display 
custom content added by the researcher.</p> 

<table width="940">
<tr>
<td valign="top" style="font-size:12px;line-height:16px;padding-top:23px;">
Name, degrees and contact information are imported from campus systems. <br /><br />
Profile owners may add:
<ul class="square" style="font-size:12px;line-height:16px;margin:0;">
<li>Photo</li>
<li>Education and Training</li>
<li>Awards and Honors</li>
<li>Research Overview</li>
<li>Interests</li>
<li>Featured Publications</li>
<li>Faculty Mentoring</li>
<li>Student Projects</li>
<li>Twitter and other feeds</li>
<li>Videos</li>
<li>Websites</li>
<li>News Links</li>
</ul>
<br />
Research Activities and Funding come from NIH ExPORTER. Other grants <br />may be added.
<br /><br /><br />Published articles available <br />
in PubMed are listed automatically. Other <span style="white-space:nowrap">publications may be added.</span>
</td>
<td valign="top"><img src="images/profilesnapshot.png" width="600" alt="" /></td>
<td valign="top" style="font-size:12px;line-height:16px;padding-top:23px;">
Networks are generated from research available in PubMed.
<br /><br /><br />
Research concepts/topics <span style="white-space:nowrap">based on PubMed MeSH terms</span><br /><br /><br /><br />
Co-authors from the same institution<br /><br /><br /><br /><br /><br />
Co-authors from external institutions<br /><br /><br /><br /><br /><br />
Researchers working on the same topics
</td>
</tr>
</table>
<p>Many researchers also have Clinical Trials information based on trials listed in clinicaltrials.gov.</p>
  
<h2 id="faq" class="about">Frequently Asked Questions</h2>
<ul> 
  <li><a href="#who">Who is listed in UCSD Profiles?</a></li>
  <li><a href="#view">Who can view UCSD Profiles?</a></li>
  <li><a href="#login">How do I sign in to UCSD Profiles?</a></li>
  <li><a href="#pubs">Why are there missing or incorrect publications in my profile? How can I correct this?</a></li>
  <li><a href="#proxy">Can someone manage my profile page for me?</a></li>
  <li><a href="#manage">Who manages UCSD Profiles?</a></li>
</ul>

<h3 id="who">Who is listed in UCSD Profiles?</h3>

<ul>
  <li>UCSD Profiles was created for research networking so we initially focused on adding UCSD faculty members, 
  researchers with academic leadership appointments, and non-faculty academic researchers. 
<p><span class="notice">Important Note: </span>
If you are a faculty member and your profile page is not found, it is most likely that your title in Blink is not listed 
with your academic faculty title. For example, if you listed your department name as your title in blink, you would have 
to change blink to reflect either Professor, Research Scientists etc. Blink updates have to be initiated either by the UCSD 
employee directly or their home department. Once blink is updated, your profile will be automatically generated with the next refresh cycle.</p>
</li>
  <li>We are happy to include research staff and other individuals in the UCSD community, on request and if possible.</li>
  <li>Profile creation requires that an individual's data be in the UCSD Directory (Blink) and set to be shared with public websites. 
  If you are a UCSD employee and do not have a profile, <a href="mailto:ctri-support@ucsd.edu">request yours now</a> 
  by sending us your UCSD Employee ID.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="view">Who can view UCSD Profiles?</h3>
<ul>
  <li>UCSD Profiles is searchable on the web and can be viewed by the general public as well as the UCSD community.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="login">How do I sign in to UCSD Profiles?</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Click the <strong><a href="../login/default.aspx?method=login&amp;edit=true">Sign in</a></strong> link on any UCSD Profiles page. 
  Then enter your SSO username and password.</li>
  <li>If you have never used SSO or for password support: go to 
  <a href="http://blink.ucsd.edu/technology/network/access/business-systems/access.html" title="Go to the UCSD Blink website" target="_blank">http://blink.ucsd.edu/technology/network/access/business-systems/access.html</a> 
  or contact your Home Departmental Administrator.</li> 
</ul>

<h3 id="pubs">Why are there missing or incorrect publications in my profile? How can I correct this?</h3> 
<ul>
  <li>UCSD Profiles uses a complex mix of names, institution, and manually entered publication information to find your publications 
  in PubMed's repository. Unfortunately, there is no easy way to exactly match all articles in PubMed to UCSD authors with complete 
  precision and accuracy. The algorithm used to find articles from PubMed attempts to minimize the number of publications incorrectly 
  added to a profile; however, this method may result in some missing or incorrectly listed publications.</li>
  <li>People who have common names, who published under multiple names or whose articles were written at other institutions are most 
  likely to have incomplete publication lists. </li>
  <li>You can make corrections by manually searching PubMed from within Profiles to add, edit or delete publications. By curating 
  publications manually, you are helping UCSD Profiles to identify which concepts and co-authors are correctly associated with your 
  profile, thereby increasing the likelihood of finding the right publications on subsequent attempts. </li>
</ul>

<h3 id="proxy">Can someone manage my profile page for me?</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Yes. Proxies are people within Profiles who can edit other people's profiles on their behalf. For example, faculty can designate 
  their assistants as proxies to edit their profiles. If you have a profile, then one or more proxies might be assigned to you automatically 
  by your department or institution. You also have the option of designating your own proxies by signing in and going to Manage Proxies in 
  the edit menu. Proxies do not need to have profile pages themselves.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="manage">Who manages UCSD Profiles?</h3>
<ul>
  <li>UCSD Profiles is managed by the UC San Diego
<a href="https://actri.ucsd.edu/Pages/default.aspx" target="_blank">Altman Clinical and Translational Research Institute (ACTRI)</a>.</li>
</ul>

          </Param>
        </ParamList>
      </Module>
      <Panel Type="passive"/>
      <Panel type="footer" />
    </Panel> 
  </PanelList>
</Presentation>

