<Presentation PresentationClass="profile">
  <PageOptions Columns="2"/>
  <WindowName>New Features</WindowName>  
  <PageTitle>New Features</PageTitle>
  <PageBackLinkName></PageBackLinkName>
  <PageBackLinkURL></PageBackLinkURL>
  <PageSubTitle></PageSubTitle>
  <PageDescription></PageDescription>  
  <PanelList>
    <Panel type="header"  />
    <Panel type="page" />
    <Panel Type="active">
      <Module ID="MainMenu"/>
    </Panel>
    <Panel Type="main">
      <Module ID="HTMLBlock">
        <ParamList>
          <Param Name="HTML">

<script type="text/javascript">
$('#suckerfishmenu li#about a').addClass('active'); 
</script><style type="text/css">
ul li { padding-top: 10px; }
#new-features { display: none; }
</style>

<p>We've made improvements to UCSF Profiles to make it an even more effective research networking and collaboration tool. Below is a summary of recent enhancements. Please <a href="mailto:profiles@ucsf.edu?Subject=New%20Features%20Feedback">share any comments</a>.</p>

<div style="border: 1px solid #CCC; padding:5px 15px; margin-bottom: 10px;">
<h2 class="about">Highlights</h2>
<ul class="highlights"> 
  <li><strong>Add All Your Funding Sources</strong> in addition to the NIH.
  </li>
  <li><strong>Discover Clinical Trials</strong> led by UCSF investigators.
  </li>
  <li><strong>View Dashboard</strong> display of statistics about visits to your personal profile page.
  </li>
  <li><strong>Explore External Co-Author</strong> networks to connect with experts at other institutions.
  </li>
  <li><strong>Showcase most important publications</strong> in their own section.
  </li>
  <li><strong>View PMCIDs and free articles</strong>  of many publications.
  </li>
  <li><strong>Build a custom list of researchers</strong> to precisely target opportunities and invitations. 
  </li>
  <li><strong>Post video lectures and talks</strong> from a variety of hosting services, e.g. Vimeo, YouTube, etc.
  </li>
</ul>

<h3 style="font-size: 14px;padding-left:38px">And there's more. See other new features and details below.</h3>
</div>

<ul>
  <li><strong>Research Activities and Funding</strong> 
      <ul>
		<li>Replaces the old "Awarded Grants" section.
		</li>
		<li>Search NIH from within UCSF Profiles to import, or manually enter any others.
		</li>
		<li><a href="../login/default.aspx?method=login&amp;edit=true">Sign in</a> to add yours!
		</li>
      </ul>
	  <img src="../App_Themes/UCSF/Images/funding.png" alt="Options for editing research activities" style="margin:10px 0 0 40px;border:1px solid #CCC;" class="screenshot" />
  </li>
  <li><strong>Clinical Trials</strong> 
      <ul>
		<li>Data collected from <a href="https://clinicaltrials.gov/" target="_blank">ClincalTrials.gov</a>.
		</li>
		<li>Researchers can feature or hide individual trials.
		</li>
      </ul>
	  <img src="../App_Themes/UCSF/Images/clinicaltrials.png" alt="Clinical Trials for Chip Chambers" style="margin:10px 0 0 40px;border:1px solid #CCC;" class="screenshot" />
  </li>
  <li><strong>Dashboard of UCSF Profiles Page Statistics</strong> - sign in access only 
      <ul>
		<li>Compiles and presents statistics about visits to your personal profile page.
		</li>
		<li>Shows you how many visits, what organizations visit your page and when. 
			<ul>
				<li>Summary stats of by-month views for the past year, this month, best month, and cumulative views</li>
				<li>Regional breakdown of visits for the last 30 days and past year</li>
				<li>Views by internet service provider or company, last 30 days and past year</li>
			</ul>
		</li>
	  </ul>
	  <img src="../App_Themes/UCSF/Images/dashboard.png" alt="Dashboard" style="margin:10px 0 0 68px;border:1px solid #CCC;" class="screenshot" />
  </li>
  <li><strong>External Co-Authors</strong>
      <ul>
		<li>Shows network of co-authors at other institutions, where that data is available.
		</li>
		<li>Name links to the co-author's page at their institution.
		</li>
		<li>Researchers can more easily connect with experts at other institutions by following these networks.
		</li>
		<li>'See all' link with new graphics (below left) opens page showing map view of co-authorships.
			<ul>
				<li>Ranked list of co-authors</li>
				<li>Links to co-authored papers</li>
			</ul>
		</li>
	  </ul>
	  <img src="../App_Themes/UCSF/Images/extCoAuth.png" alt="External Co-Authors" style="margin:10px 0 0 40px;" />
  </li>
  <li><strong>Featured Publications</strong>
      <ul>
		<li>Makes a researcher's most important publications more visible by placing them above the fold and distinguished from chronological list of publications.
		</li>
		<li>This helps researchers showcase their best work and set it apart from their full body of work. 
		</li>
		<li>Profile owner or proxy can select publications to emphasize.
			<ul>
				<li>All publications in the person's profile are available to add</li>
				<li>Drag and drop to re-order them in editing screen</li>
			</ul>
		</li>
	  </ul>
	  <img src="../App_Themes/UCSF/Images/featuredPubs.png" alt="Featured Publications Example" style="margin:10px 0 0 68px;border:1px solid #CCC;" class="screenshot" />
  </li>
  <li><strong>Publications Data</strong>
      <ul>
		<li>PMCIDs now included for articles that have them.  This helps researchers and faculty easily access these IDs. 
		</li>
		<li>All users can click through to free full-text articles when they are available. 
		</li>
		<li>Altmetric statistics show how an article is being accessed and shared on social media. This gives users and authors an early indication of the popularity of a paper, well in advance of citations or other traditional metrics.
		</li>
	  </ul>
  </li>
  <li><strong>ListMaker</strong> - sign in access only (<a href="../about/ListMakerGuidance.pdf" target="_blank">instructions</a>)
      <ul>
		<li>Build a custom list of people from search results, network 'See All' pages and individual pages, then export contact info, compose an email or send them a Doodle Poll.
		</li>
		<li>Cut down on email spam by precisely targeting outreach, e.g. invite neuroinflammation researchers to a seminar or notify juvenile diabetes researchers about an opportunity from the Juvenile Diabetes Research Foundation. 
		</li>
	  </ul>
	  <img src="../App_Themes/UCSF/Images/listMaker.png" alt="ListMaker Example" style="margin:10px 0 0 40px;" />
  </li>		
  <li><strong>Featured Videos</strong>
      <ul>
		<li>Researchers can post lectures, panels, techniques, or any other recorded activity.
		</li>
		<li>Additional hosting services supported: YouTube, Vimeo, TedTalks (ted.com), UCTV and more 
		</li>
		<li>Better viewer shows multiple videos with previews in the profile page.
		</li>
	  </ul>
	  <img src="../App_Themes/UCSF/Images/featuredVideos.png" alt="Featured Videos Example" style="margin:10px 0 0 90px;border:1px solid #CCC;" class="screenshot" />
  </li>
  <li><strong>New Search Options</strong><br />
      UCSF Profiles now allows you to search by a keyword or concept and return not only the 
      list of experts at UCSF (6000+) but also all recent papers from UCSF on a topic.<br />
      <img src="images/conceptsearch.jpg" alt="Search Options" style="margin:10px 0 0 90px" class="screenshot" />
  </li>
  <li><strong>Highlight Your Interests</strong><br />
      The feature most requested by profile owners over the last 2 years has been the option to 
      add customized keywords that reflect personal interests. Now you can! Your customized and searchable 
      keywords complement the existing automatically generated concepts derived from publications.     
  </li>
  <li><strong>Personalized URLs</strong><br />
      It's now easy to remember your profile page web address, and to share it on business cards,
      email signatures, etc. Your new USCF Profiles address is based on your first and last name (e.g.
      profiles.ucsf.edu/john.smith). Find your customized address in the browser address bar when you 
      visit your profile.    
  </li>
  <li><strong>New Visualizations of Helpful Information </strong>
     <ul>
        <li><strong>View the time course of publishing and collaborations </strong>
            (e.g. assess whether someone is an expert because of a classic paper written a decade ago
            or because of recent contributions; identify recent versus long-past co-authors). To view, 
            click the Timeline link above an individual's list of publications. <br />
            <img src="../App_Themes/UCSF/Images/pubsgraph.jpg" alt="Publication timeline" style="margin:10px 0 0 45px" class="screenshot" />
        </li>
        <li><strong>Explore Networks Associated with an Expert</strong> (right column on each profile) 
            <ul> 
               <li><strong>Related Concepts</strong> includes subject areas related to an individual's 
                   publishing history. Select "See all" to view different visualizations, including a 
                   timeline that demonstrates topics an individual has published on over time. <br />  
                   <img src="../App_Themes/UCSF/Images/timeline.jpg" alt="Expertise timeline" style="margin:10px 0 0 0" class="screenshot" />
               </li>   
               <li><strong>Related Co-Authors</strong> includes subject areas related to an individual's
                   publishing history. Select "See all" to view visualizations including number of 
                   co-publications by individual, a map of co-author publications, etc.   <br />  
                   <img src="../App_Themes/UCSF/Images/detailstab.jpg" alt="Related Co-Authors" style="margin:10px 0 0 0" class="screenshot" />
               </li>   
            </ul>    
        </li>      
     </ul>
  </li>
  <li><strong>Updated Look and Feel</strong><br />
      You'll notice some subtle but helpful changes, including a new table of contents that make it
      easy to quickly review individual profiles.<br />
      <img src="../App_Themes/UCSF/Images/toc.jpg" alt="Look and Feel" style="margin:10px 0 0 80px" class="screenshot" />
  </li>
</ul>
<p><br />Do you have questions or ideas for new UCSF Profiles features? Let us know at <a href="mailo:profiles@ucsf.edu">profiles@ucsf.edu</a>. </p>
        
          </Param>
        </ParamList>
      </Module>
      <Panel Type="passive"/>
      <Panel type="footer" />
    </Panel> 
  </PanelList>
</Presentation>

